globalshopex.com 2019-08-12

# Privacy

**Privacy Policy**

Global Shopex LLC, a company based in Miami, Florida, USA, is committed to protecting customer information, how it's used and how it's shared, and we appreciate customer choosing to do business with us. This Privacy Policy describes how Globalshopex collect and use the Personal Information customer provides on Globalshopex website and as part of Our Services, including Personally Identifiable Information, Personally Identifiable Information and Anonymous Information. It also describes the choices available to customers regarding Globalshopex use of customer Personal Information and how customer can access and update this information. By visiting Globalshopex, customer are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

All terms not otherwise defined herein shall have the definitions set forth in the Terms of Service.    
This Privacy Policy, which is part of our overall Terms of Service ("Terms of Service"), covers personal information shared through our website and Our Services, including Personally Identifiable Information and Anonymous Information (the "Personal Information"). "Personally Identifiable Information" or "PII" means information that can be used to identify Customer as an individual. 

**I.   Personal Information About Customers Gathered By GlobalShopex **

**1.- Information Customer Give Us**   

We value customer privacy. GlobalShopex will receive and store the basic information customer give us during checkout in order to process and deliver their products and provide them exceptional customer support.  Customer must provide contact information (such as name, email, telephone number and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number). The information customer provide us will be used for billing purposes and to fill their orders.  

We follow CAN SPAM laws and offer permission based email marketing.  If customer do not wish for us to contact customer about offers that may interest them, customer may uncheck the opt-in feature in the checkout, or opt-out from the emails themselves by following the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of any e-mail message customer receive from GlobalShopex. 

**2.- What DATA does Globalshopex collect?   
**

We may collect the following Data: 

  * International customer email must be provided if they wish to create a user account, communicate with Globalshopex thanks to the contact forms.    

  * Data relating to customer identity, such as their First Name, Name and email, may be required on detail collection forms. 
  * Customer Globalshopex User ID and password (if applicable). 
  * For some countries such as Russia, India, and countries in Latin America, we collect passport and ID information required for Customs to clear customer products in each country.    

  * Phone number, billing address, and shipping address.    

  * Any account-preference information provided by customer.    

  * Data relating to browsing: Data relating to how customer use the Websites, including: IP address, browser used, browsing duration, search history, operating system used, language and pages viewed.    

  * Data about customer visits to our Website, including traffic data, log files and other data or communication resources used by customer when accessing our Websites.    

  * Orders Data: customer mailing address is required to draw up invoices. Customer bank or PayPal details have to be provided to pay customer order.    

  * Data about social network use when customer use those features.    

**3.-Why is Customer DATA collected?**

Customer Data is collected by Globalshopex for the following purposes: 

  * Manage the orders and fulfil the contract.    

  * Ensure the security and traceability of purchases.    

  * Transmit customer information regarding customer user account (invoices, orders history).    

  * Manage customer requests communicated via the help center, and/or by the chat software. Chat software provided to users is handled by the Freshdesk software, published by Freshworks Inc. – 1250 Bayhill Drive, Suite 315, San Bruno, CA 94066 – USA. This company is a member of the “Privacy Shield” framework ensuring that it offers sufficient guarantees regarding customer Data protection.    

  * Notify the changes on our Websites or in our offering of products and services.    

  * Respect our rights and obligations stipulated in the agreements concluded with the users and for any other lawful purposes.    

  * Ensure the security and traceability of purchases.    

  * Enabling our Websites to recognize customer equipment, saving customer from having to provide the same information several times to perform the same task.    

  * Analyzing Websites traffic and data to measure the number of users and subsequently make the Website easier to use and ensure it is able to quickly respond to customer requests. The refusal to provide some Data could lead to the unavailability of certain services.    
Respect our rights and obligations stipulated in the agreements concluded with the users and for any other lawful purposes. Customer Data may also be collected via cookies and tracers, with customer consent when required,    

**4.-We will not use or disclose any such Personal Data, except:   
**

  * As necessary to provide the Services to Customer.    

  * As required by law, or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law;    

  * To outside auditors who have agreed to keep the information confidential;    

  * To a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, or other sale or disposition of all or a portion of our assets;    

  * As necessary to enforce Our Terms of Service;    

  * As necessary to protect Our rights, safety, or property, Our users, or others; this may include (for example) exchanging information with other organizations for fraud protection and/or risk reduction; and    

  * As otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or to which customer have consented.    
We do not sell, rent or trade Customer Personal Information to third parties. We will not use any DATA we collect from customers to contact or market customers.    

**II . Personal Data Security and Confidentiality   
**

We maintain adequate technical and organizational security measures to protect customer personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

**1.-Third Parties**

If customer purchase, use or specifically express interest in a product or service of one of our partners, we may share Personal Information about customer with such partner. 

We use third party payment processors and fraud screening to assist us in processing and share with them customer payment information securely. Such third party processors’ use of customer Personal Information is governed by their respective privacy policies which may or may not contain privacy protections as protective as this privacy policy. 

We may use other third parties to help us provide services and marketing to customer, such as shipping or fulfilling orders, processing payments, monitoring site activity, identifying and preventing fraud, conducting quality assurance and testing, providing support, conducting surveys, and administering e-mails, and share with them customer Personal Information solely for those purposes. 

If we share any Personal Information with any of these third parties, we will require that such information be used only to provide the services requested by us and be maintained by them in strictest confidence. 

We do not control the use by third parties of customer Personal Information that we collect, and its use by them will be in accordance with their own privacy policies. However, we will ensure that they are bound by agreements with us that include non-disclosure and certain data protection provisions. If customer do not wish for customer Personal Information to be shared in this manner, customer may opt not to purchase or use these third party services or to specifically express interest in our partner products or services. 

We will always ask for customer consent before sharing customer Personal Information with Third Parties for purposes other than those described herein.    

**2.- Cookies and Opting Out**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to customer computer's hard drive through customer Web browser to enable our systems to recognize customer browser and to provide certain features and improve our business. 

The help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell customer how to prevent customer browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify customer when customer receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, customer can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow customer to take advantage of some of GlobalShopex's essential features, we recommend that customer leave them turned on. For instance, if customer block or otherwise reject our cookies, customer will not be able to add items to customer Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or to Sign in to GlobalShopex's website.    

**3.-Third Party Tags and content**

We use and manage third party tags on Our Site. Third party tags may take the form of pixels or tracking snippets. This means that no cookies are used and no personal data is collected. We use Google Tag Manager to manage our third party tag usage. We use tracking snippets to capture data from customer browser, make requests to a third party partner or set cookies on customer device to store data. This may cause other tags to be activated which may, for their part, collect data and set cookies under certain circumstances. Google Tag Manager does not access or store this data.    

**III. Information Security**

We work to protect the security of customer information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information customer input. 

We will take commercially reasonable precautions to protect customer information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We follow industry standards on information security management to safeguard sensitive information, and are certified as a PCI-DSS service provider. Our platform is audited annually by a third-party qualified security assessor for compliance with PCI-DSS.    

**IV. Data Retention**

We will retain customer Personal Information for as long as customer Account is active or for as long as needed to provide Customers or our users with the Services. We also retain Customer Personal Information for legitimate business purposes and to comply with the law. The precise periods for which we retain customer Personal Information vary depending on the nature of the information or why we need it. We collect and retain indefinitely anonymous information, such as website visits, in order to improve our Services. Data collected within the scope of Website use are hosted by Webhosting.net Inc, whose servers are located at NAP of the Americas, Miami, Florida in the United States. As such, customer Data may be transferred outside of the European Union, to the United States for hosting purposes. By using the Website, customer agree to customer Data being transferred to those servers.    

**V. What are customer rights?**

Customers can choose how the Data customer provide is used: 

  * Customer can browse the Website without providing Data. This means customer will be unable to use certain Websites features and, in particular, purchase and/or download Connectors/Extensions on the Website from third parties, partners and e-Commerce platforms.    

  * Customer can refuse to provide their credit card, bank or PayPal details and/or postal address. In this case, customer will not be able to purchase    

  * Customer can decide to no longer receive our Newsletter and personalized offers. In this case, customer can unsubscribe by clicking on the link in the email.    

However, in accordance with Article 12.6 of the GDPR, when customer exercise these rights, Globalshopex, as the controller, reserves the right to require proof of customer identity. Customer must be aware that the data required to prove their identity will be deleted once we have responded to their request. Customer can exercise their rights by sending an email in English or Spanish to info@globalshopex.com or writing to: 

GlobalShopex    
9990 NW 14th St Suite 110    
Miami, FL 33172    
United States    
Tel: 1-855-848 8804    
We are required to reply within one (1) month to all requests regarding the exercising of these rights. This timeframe may be extended to two (2) months for complex requests and large request volumes. 

**VI. Residents of the European Economic Area**

Our operations are located in the United States. If customer are located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), customer Personal Information will be transferred out of the European Economic Area to the United States. Residents of the EEA have certain rights under European law with respect to customer personal data, including the right to request access to, correct, amend, delete or limit the use of customer personal data. If customer are a resident of the EEA and Our customer or partner or a User of Our Site and Customer wish to exercise these rights, please contact us at customercare@globalshopex.com. If customers are a resident of the EEA, we note that we are generally processing customer information in order to fulfill our obligations under contracts we have with customer (including our Terms of Service), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests as described in this Privacy Policy, unless we are required by law to obtain customer consent for a particular processing operation.    

**VII. Choices Regarding Customer Personal Information**

We understand that and value customer rights over customer Personal Information. We have taken steps to allow customers to access, correct, amend, delete or port customer Personal Information and give customers choices regarding the collection, use and sharing of customer Personal Information. Customer may manage their receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of our marketing emails. If customer are unable to change their Personal Information within Account settings, or if customer are concerned about data collected as customer visit our site, please contact us at customercare@globalshopex.com. If Please understand that if customer delete or limit the use of their Personal Information, the Services may not function properly or certain Services may not be available. 

**VIII. Terms of Service, Notices, And Revisions**

If customer choose to visit GlobalShopex, their visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our Terms of Service, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Florida. 

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but customer should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. It is customer responsibility to review this document periodically for changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about customer and their account. 

If customer have any questions or disputes of this Privacy Policy arise, please contact GlobalShopex at info@GlobalShopex, and we will do our best to answer or resolve customer issue. Customer may also choose to contact us by mail at: 

GlobalShopex    
9990 NW 14th St Suite 110    
Miami, FL 33172    
United States    
Tel: 1-855-848 8804
